ACTWU New England Regional Joint Board Records 5619/045
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU New England Regional Joint Board Records
1939-2002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
5619/045
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Records (documents), correspondence.
7544854
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 24, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Biographical / Historical
The New England Regional Joint Board included representatives from locals in the six-state New England area. It represented workers in the men's and boy's clothing, shirt, sportswear, single pants and cotton garment, women's and children's apparel, parachute, electric blanket, and rope industries throughout New England. Members also worked in the brush and plastics, laundry, retail workers, dye-finishing and custom tailoring industries. The main headquarters was in North Dartmouth, Massachusetts.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5619: ACWA Records 5619 AV: ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials 5619 C-S MB: ACTWU President Jack Sheinkman Additional Books, Memorabilia, and Files 5619 F: ACTWU Motion Picture Films 5619 G: ACTWU Graphics 5619 MB: ACTWU Memorabilia Collection 5619 mf: ACWA Records Parts 1-3 on Microfilm 5619 OH: ACWA Oral History Project Records 5619 P: ACTWU Photographs 5619 PUBS: ACTWU Publications 5619/001: ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/002: ACWA Education Department Records 5619/003: ACWA Sidney Hillman Scrapbooks 5619/004: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004 fiche: ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Speeches on Microfiche 5619/005: ACWA Bessie Hillman Papers 5619/006: ACTWU Executive Vice-President's Office Files 5619/007: ACTWU Organizing Department Files 5619/008: ACWA Rieve-Pollock Foundation Files 5619/009: ACTWU Operations Department Sidney Hillman Awards Files 5619/010: ACWA Jacob Potofsky files 5619/011: ACTWU Southern Regional Joint Board Files 5619/012: ACTWU Company Files 5619/013: ACTWU Research Department Correspondence Chronological Files 5619/014: ACWA Local 169 Files
Textile industry -- New York (State) -- New York; Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing trade -- New York (State) -- New York; Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State) -- New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization)
7544854
- Arbitration decisions. (Box 1)
  - Arthur Moran, Jerry Miller I.D. seniority, Tim Bornstein Arbitration, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    April 18 1990
  - Arbitration Decision Kivy Casuals, Amelia Boucher, Edward C. Pinkus, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Cut in piece rate after trial period
  - Arbitration Decision Lesnow Manufacturing, Marilyn Donoven, Morris Horowitz, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    February 23 1989
  - Arbitration Decision, Lesnow Manufacturing, Morris Horowitz, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Cutting room minimum rate and progression
  - Arbitration Decision, Lesnow Manufacturing, Herman Greenberg, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    February 12 1974
  - Letter of the New England Regional Director of ACWA-AFL-CIO; CLC (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Manchester Knitted Fashions, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    March 2 1987
  - Manchester Knitted Fashions Arbitration Decision Arbitrator Higgins, Cheryl Wilson, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Layoffs
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Cumberland, Rhode Island, Shipping Room, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Stockmen; May, 1978
  - Health-Tex, C.F. #77-130B-MC., 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Rate settings for new or changed operations, September 1977
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, #77-130C-MC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Knitting Room suspension of 5 employees, September 1977
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    "Piece work' average for 3rd quarter 1975; July 1976
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Open shoulder rates on operations 37 and 38, Department 53; April 1975
  - Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Oscar Rainville Discharge; 11/11/1976
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Josephine Byrd discharge, November 1976
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Charles Havers discharge; July 1976
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Santos Discharge; December 1974
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Fork-lift driver rate; December 1974
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Garment Inspector rate; December 1974
  - Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Beverly Desrosiers discharge; September 6 1973
  - Health-Tex, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Termination without just cause
  - Health-Tex, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Truck Driver's interest
  - Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Health-Tex Maine, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Re: Layoff; May 29 1988
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Power Failure; May 29 1988
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Article 24 Vacation Pay Violation, May 1988
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    Lamontagne, January 1988
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Violation of Article I; January 1988
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Grievance No. 8882 and 8883 (August 7 1987) and Grievance No. 8965 and 5697 (November 6 1987)
  - Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Helen Tardiff; January 1988; Ross
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Work saver drivers; January 1988 Ross
  - Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Lamonte Holt Discharge; November 1987
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Dale Precourt discharge; September 1987
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Martha LaPorte; June 1987; Ross
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Chairs; February 16 1987; Ross
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Mechanics Overtime Pay; April 1987
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Lamphone Voravongsa discharge; December 1986
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Timothy Bourgault discharge; December 1986
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Elm Avenue price ticket-making machine rate; February 18 1986
  - Health-Tex (Martin Street Annex), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Piece rates
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Martin Street Annex, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    re: Power Failure; March 30 1982
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Diamond Hill, Dryer Operation, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Technological change rate; March 30 1982
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    Maria Rosario, Maria Simao, No. 80-9
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    Collarette Operation Rates; August 1980
  - Arbitration Decision, Central Falls, No. 80-3B-MC, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    Tote dispatchers, packing room, 10 cents; April 1980
  - Arbitration Decision, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    Discharges Lewis, Dalton, Duquette; April 15 1980
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Diamond Hill, No. 80-6C-MC, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Vieira, Figueiredo; Shift differential; April 16 1980
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Central Falls, No. 79-17A-MC, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Lucia Lumb; August 29 1979
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Roll handlers; August 29 1979
  - Nellie Barisi, Local 615, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    October 8 1981
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Maine, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    Subcontracting; February 16 1987; Ross
  - van Baalen Cutters (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Maine, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    Piece Rate "Join Shoulders"; April 11 1984
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Maine, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Proux discharge; February 6 1984
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Maine, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Maine Boxers; October 7 1983; Cass
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Portland, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Ann Frank; August 16 1983; Cass
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Portland, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Vacation pay; August 16 1983; Cass
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Portland, No. 77-119B-MC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    lay-off, trainee works; August 1977
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Central Falls; 80-3A-MC, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Protective gloves; J. Rodriguez; April 1980
  - Health-Tex, Maine, Settled Arbitrations (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Health-Tex, Gardiner, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Pin and Fold Maintenance of Earnings Settlement
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, No. 77-A-MC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Layoff work available in other plants; September 1977
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Portland, Maine (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Askew, Barker
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Portland, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Saunders unfairly docked; November 1982; Cass
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Maine, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    Violation of Subcontract and Stable Work Clauses; May 1981
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Maine, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    Local Issues; March 1980
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Gardiner, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    Stephen Smart; November 14 1979
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Gardiner, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    Roger La Brie; November 14 1979
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Gardiner, Maine, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    Rime Study; No. 78-146; October 1978
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Portland, No. 77-119C-MC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    Retraining Incentive Project; August 1977
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Gardiner, Maine, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    William Bewell; No. 77-119A; August 1977
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Portland, No. 77-119D-MC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    Operation rate, Notch and Sew; August 1977
  - Health-Tex, Brunswick, No. 77-132-MC, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    Discharge of Dorothy Salac; October 1977
  - Health-Tex, Portland, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    Collarette Rates; June 1972
  - Health-Tex, Brunswick, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    Production Standard Operation 10 Boy's Boxers; October 1968
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    February 18 1986; Holiday pay; Martin Street
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    Rates: Leferriere, et al; Annex; September 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    Interest Arbitration; June 25 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    Holiday Pay; April 17 1985; Scearce
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    Local demands; August 1983
  - Health-Tex, Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    Cutting Room Tie Up Operation Equal Rights; August 24 1983
  - Health-Tex and Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    Truck Drivers and Mike Gagne; August 23 1983; Cass
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    Martin Street Annex hiring of non-bargain unit employees; August 1983
  - Health-Tex Closing, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    February 14 1990; Michael Stutz-Arbitrator
  - basil Madjoucoff, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    Appeal September 1989
  - Eugene Viveiros Health-Tex, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    L. Foy Arbitration Five Day Suspension; December 14 1989
  - Arbitration Decision, Health-Tex, Rhode Island, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    Sheila Gardner; February 1986
  - Health-Tex, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    Philip Ross; Lamonte Holt; November 6 1987
  - Health-Tex, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    Philip Ross; Timothy Bourgault; January 6 1987
  - Debra Johnson-Justin, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    January 29 1990 Lay-off; September 7 1989 Professor Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Justin Clothing, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    Maria Rezendes; March 4 1988
  - Arbitration decision, Justin Clothing, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    Joseph Silveira; March 28 1988
  - Arbitration Decision, Justin Clothing, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    Vacation Pay; November 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, Justin Clothing, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    Amaral suspension; January 18 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, Justin Clothing, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    Joaquina Bogalha Discharge
  - Justin Clothing, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Arbitration Decision, Justin Clothing, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    Piecework Average; November 6 1991; Professor Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Justin Clothing, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    Seniority and Cutting Room; February 1975; Professor Horowitz
  - Justin Clothing, San-Toro Seniority Grievance, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    Soaba, Fuse front; October 22 1996
  - Arbitration decision, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    Ernest Campolini, 1982 Grieco; Professor M. Horowitz, Arbitrator
  - Grieco-Gilberto Javier, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    Investigation; January 16 1990; L. Schneider
  - Maintenance of earnings, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    Grieco and ACTWU; April 29 1986
  - Arbitration Decision, Grieco, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    Pressers' Grievance; March 24 1986
  - Arbitration Decision, Grieco Brothers, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    Finish pressers piece rate grievance; March 24 1986
  - Hathaway, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Arbitration Decision, Hathaway Company, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    Various Issues; September 24 1984; Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, C.F. Hathaway Company, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    Wesley Davis Discharge; August 4 1982; Cass
  - Arbitration Decision, C.F. Hathaway Company, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    Piece cut rate inspection and box main of earning; August 1982; Cass
  - Hathaway Shirt, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    Gary Gorman discharge; June 27 1995
  - Arbitration Decision, Hathaway Shirt, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    Quirion September 1981
  - Eastern Sportswear, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 113)
    Computation of piece work increases; January 8 1990; Professor Horowitz
  - Eastern Sports, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    Computation of rates; January 17 1990; Professor Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Fall River Shirt, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    Premium pay for holidays; February 28 1991; Professor Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Filene's, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    Issue: Article XVII failure to recall from layoff; 1982
  - Freedberg Subcontracting, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    January 20 1993; Professor Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Arthur Freedberg, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    Holiday pay hours grievance; April 18 1986
  - Arbitration Decision, G.T., Inc., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    Corduroy pants and Summer vacation pay; September 12 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, G.T., Inc., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    Subcontracting under Clothing agreement; November 1984; Horowitz
  - Friction Materials, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 121)
    Holiday Award; July 1989; R. Higgins
  - Arbitration Decision, Gentlemen's Wear House, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    Pro-Rata Vacation pay; January 15 1985
  - Arbitration Decision, Gentlemen's Wear House, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 123)
    4th Day sick pay; November 22 1983; Littom
  - Gentlemen's Wear House, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Arbitration Decision, Dartmouth Clothing, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 125)
    4th Week Vacation Pay (20 Years); October 1983
  - Arbitration Decision, Darwood, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 126)
    Layoff entitled to Holiday Pay; 1977; Pinkus
  - Arbitration Decision, Darwood Manufacturing Company, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 127)
    Wage increase; October 18 1983; Horowitz
  - Harvard Cooperation Society, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Arbitration Decision, Briggs, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 129)
    Holiday hours during week; Albert Hoban
  - Brooks Brothers, Joseph Amato, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 130)
    May 18 1981
  - Arbitration Decision, Atlantic Department Stores, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 131)
    Closed store severance pay, unused sick leave
  - Eastern Sportswear Manufacturing Company, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - ACTWU, Local 1 and 181 G.T., Inc., 1984 (Box 1, Folder 133)
    Arbitration Decision; Subcontracting; Professor Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Essex, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 134)
    Bonus pay for holiday and vacation; August 28 1987
  - Arbitration decision, Leon Clothing Manufacturing, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 135)
    Bonus and Meola jury duty pay; September 9 1987; Horowitz
  - Arbitration Decision, Yale Genton, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 136)
    Qualified fitters vs. seniority; Horowitz
  - Arbitration, Davis Clothing, Boston, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 137)
    Mark Carlson; June 1979
- Arbitration decisions. (Box 2)
  - Dye craftsmen, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Layoffs, sick leave, and insurance grievances; Arbitrator A. Zack; December 16 1992
  - Arbitration Appeal, Loretta Carey, Dorothy Proulx, Isabelle Leal, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    October 1989
  - Dye Craftsmen, Manuel Moitoso, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    'Overtime dispute; Arbitrator James Cooper; September 1988
  - Arbitration Award Francisco Miranda, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Floor plan person rate; Arbitrator Lawrence Katz; October 31 1989